Oh,here's little Ben falling asleep.
哦,小本本困了
A little bit later. Is he gonna sleep?
等一下,他就要睡着了
Is he gonna sleep? Is he gonna?
他要睡了吗?要睡了吗?
Yep,out like a light!
是的,就是这个了!
This sure trumps the "Has he pooped?" series.
这一定是强普的“他筋疲力竭了?”系列
Ross,we love him,okay?
罗斯,我们爱他,ok?
But right now he's just a little fat guy.
但是现在他只是一个裸体的胖小伙
How excited can we get?
我们实在是太兴奋了?
-What you got? -400 pictures of Ben on a rug.
-你拿的什么? -本垫子下的400张照片
-Oh,my God! -Let me see!
-哦,天哪! -让我看看!
The One Where Rachel Finds Out
六人行 第1季 第24集 瑞秋恍然大悟
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
Here's little Ben nodding off.
小本本睡着了
Look at Aunt Monica's little boy!
看摩妮卡姑姑的小男孩
-Look,he's got Ross haircut. -Let me see.
-瞧,他有罗斯的发型. -我看看
Oh,God! Is he just the sweetest thing?
天啊,真可爱
You must just wanna kiss him all over.
你一定想吻遍他
That would be nice.
那感觉一定很好
-Pardon? -Nothing.
-什么? -没事
Just a little extra air in my mouth.
只是嘴里有多余的空气
Chan,can you help me out? I'll pay you back.
钱德,愿意帮我吗?我保证一定会还的
Right. Including the waffles last week,you now owe me...
好,包括上星期的威化饼,你现在欠我
... 1 7 jillion dollars.
17大洋
-Really,I'll pay you back this time. -Where's this money coming from?
-真的,这一次我真的会还 -钱将从哪儿来?
I'm helping out at the NYU Med School with research.
我正帮纽约大学医学院做一些研究
What kind of research?
什么研究?
Just,you know,science.
只不过,你知道的,科学研究
Science.
科学?
Yeah,I think I've heard of that.
我想我听说过
It's a fertility study.
生殖研究
Joey,please tell me you're only donating your time.
乔伊,请告诉我你只贡献时间
Actually,a little more than that.
事实上,比这稍微多一点点
Thank you,God. This will bring us so much joy.
谢谢,上帝.这会给我们带来更多笑料
Come on,it's not that big a deal.
拜托,这没什么了不起的
I just go down there every other day...
我只是两天去一趟
...and make my contribution to the project.
对此计划贡献己力
But at the end of two weeks, I get $700!
但两周后我就有七百元
You're gonna be making money hand over fist.
你将“靠手”赚钱
That's funny. Very funny.
这太有趣了,非常有趣
This is great. I actually know somebody who loves what they do.
太好了,我真的知道有人非常喜欢他们做的
But what do you do to unwind after a tough day at work?
但是一天的辛苦工作后,你怎么放松自己呢?
Okay,we got the coleslaw and buns.
我们有酸卷心菜丝,小面包
The ground-up flesh of formerly cute cows and turkeys.
还有绞牛肉及火鸡肉
I just love barbecuing with you.
我喜欢和你一起出去烤肉
Men are here!
男人回来了
We make fire.
我们生火
Cook meat.
煮肉
Put out fire by peeing, no get invited back.
然后撒尿熄火,从此成为拒绝往来户
Cute.
真逗
-Melanie called. She'll be late. -Okay.
-玛莲妮来电说她会迟到. -好
How are things going? Is she becoming your "special someone"?
你们俩进展得如何?她会成为你的女友?
I don't know. She's pretty great.
我不知道,她很好
What does she think of your little science project?
是吗?她对你的研究计划有何感想?
You think I'd tell a girl I like that I'm also seeing a cup?
你认为我会告诉她,我也和“杯子”约会?
Man's got a point.
男人是有重点的
The tough thing is, she really wants to have sex.
麻烦的是她想和我做爱
Crazy bitch.
这娘儿们疯了
I got a week left to go. According to the rules...
此计划我只剩一星期,根据规定
... I can't conduct personal experiments,if you know what I mean.
如果我想拿到钱,我就不能做“个人”实验 如果你们懂我意思的话
Joey,we always know what you mean.
乔伊,我们永远都了解你
How long did you think this barbecue would last?
你以为烤肉会维持多久?
-I'm going to China. -Jeez,you say one thing,and....
-我要去中国了 -你说一件事…
-China? -For the museum. Someone found a bone.
-你要去中国? -对,为博物馆出差,有人找到骨头
They don't want us to have it.
我们要骨头,但他们不想给我们骨头
I'm going to try to persuade them. It's a whole big bone thing.
因此派我去说服他们给我们骨头,都是骨头的事
Anyway,I'll be gone for a week.
总之,我要去一个星期
If you want to reach me,you can't. So here's my itinerary.
你们将连络不到我,这是我的行程表
-Here's a picture of me. -Oh,let me see.
-这是我的照片. -让我看
Could you show it to Ben every now and then so he doesn't forget me?
能偶尔拿照片到卡萝家去给本看? 这样他就不会忘记我了
"Hi,Ben. I'm your father."
本,我是你爸爸
"I am The Head!"
我是头
This barbecue's gonna be very fun.
这回烤肉一定很好玩
I wanted to wish Rachel a happy birthday before I left.
瑞秋在吗?我想在我离开前祝她生日快乐
-She's out having drinks with Carl. -Hey,who's Carl?
-她和卡尔在外面喝酒 -卡尔是谁?
That guy she met at the coffeehouse.
她在咖啡屋认识的那个
-There's this guy she met at -The coffeehouse? Right.
-她在咖啡屋认识的那个? -咖啡屋?是的
So you do know who he is.
这么说你知道他是谁
I'll go say goodbye to the guys.
我去跟他们道别
Hey,you know what? Tell them that bone story.
告诉他们骨头的事吧
-I have to go to China. -The country?
-我得到中国(瓷器)一趟 -国家?
No,this big pile of dishes in my mom's breakfront.
不,我妈家中的一大堆盘子
Do you know who Carl is?
你知道卡尔是谁吗?
Let's see. Alvin,Simon,Theodore.... No.
我想看看,艾文,赛门,希尔朵…不认识
Rachel's having drinks with him tonight.
瑞秋今晚和他在一起喝酒
How can she,when she's never shown interest in you?
不,她还没对你有任何表示前,怎能这样做?
-Forget about her. -He's right.
-忘了她吧 -他说得对
Please move on. Go to China. Eat Chinese food.
去吧,到中国,吃中国菜
Of course,there they just call it "food."
当然,他们在那儿只称为菜
Yeah,I guess. I don't know.
是吗?大概吧,我也不知道
All right,just give her this for me,okay?
帮我把这个交给她
We're looking out for you. We want you to be happy.
兄弟,我们只是为你着想,我们要你快乐
I may only have a couple beers in me,but I love you.
或许我喝了两瓶,但我爱你
I'm still on my first.
我只喝了一瓶
I just think you're nice.
我觉得你人真好
That's when we started this fruit basket business.
总之,我和朋友开始水果篮事业后
We call ourselves "The Three Basketeers."
我们就自称为“三篮人”
Like "The Three Musketeers," only with fruit.
就像“三个火枪手”,只不过是用蔬菜啊
-How do you want your burgers? -Presents first!
-谁想吃汉堡? -不,礼物先
We're doing presents first.
礼物先,待会儿再吃
Hey,hold on there,tiger. How are you holding up?
等等,猛男.进展得如何?
Well,not so good. She thinks tonight we're gonna...
不太顺利,她想在今晚
...complete the transaction, if you know what And you do.
就敲定这笔交易,如果你…你懂
Have you ever thought about being there for her?
曾想过要为她着想?
What do you mean?
什么意思?
You know,just be there for her.
你知道的,只为她着想
Not following you.
不懂
Think about it.
考虑一下
Okay. I'm guessing this is from....
我猜这是…
-Thank you,Melanie. -This one right here is from me.
-谢谢,玛莲妮. -这是我送你的
Okay. It's light. It rattles.
好轻,还有声音
It's...
这是…
...Travel Scrabble!
…是旅游拼字
Thank you.
谢谢
This one's from Joey.
这是乔伊送的
It feels like a book,I think it's a book. And it's a book!
感觉像是一本书,我猜是一本书,就是一本书啊!
It's Dr. Seuss!
是“苏博士”
That book got me through some tough times.
那本书让我度过许多难关
There's a little child inside this man.
这男人里面有个小孩
The doctors say if they remove it, he'll die.
医生说把他移走他就会死
-Who's this from? -From Ross.
-这是谁送的? -罗斯送的
Oh,my God! He remembered!
天啊,他记得
-Remembered what? -lt was months ago.
-记得什么? -几个月前
We walked by this antique store. I saw this pin.
我们经过一家古董店.我看见这个胸针时
I told him it was like one my grandma had when I was little.
我告诉他我小时候我祖母也有一个
I can't believe he remembered!
没想到他还记得
Well,sure,but can you play it on a plane?
但你能在飞机上玩吗?
It's so pretty! This must've cost him a fortune.
-好漂亮 -一定花了他不少钱
I can't believe it.
没想到他会这么做
Remember when he fell in love with Carol...
记得大学时代他和卡萝相恋时
...and bought her that expensive crystal duck?
他送她一只贵死人的水晶鸭?
What did you just say?
你刚说什么?
Crystal duck.
水晶鸭
No,no,no. The "love" part?
不,相恋那一部份
-Oh,my God! -Oh,no,no,no.
-天啊! -糟了,糟了
That's good. Just keep rubbing your head. That'll turn back time.
很好,继续挠你的头,时间会倒流的
This is unbelievable. I mean,this is unbelievable!
太不可思议了,真是太不可思议了
I know. This is really,really huge.
我知道,这真是太大了
No,it's not. It's small. It's tiny. It's petite. It's wee.
不,它又小又细又霉
I don't think any of our lives will ever be the same ever again.
我认为我们的生活将产生变化
Is there a mute button on this woman?
这女人身上有消音装置吗?
I think this is so great. I mean,you and Ross!
我认为这样很好啊,你和罗斯
-Did you have any idea? -No,none!
-你有感觉吗? -没有
My first night in the city, he mentioned asking me out...
我来到纽约的第一夜,他曾提过要约我出去
... but nothing ever happened.
但他后来再没提过邀我出去
What else did he say? Does he wanna go out?
他还说些什么?,他想约我出去?
Given that he's in love with you...
如果他爱你爱得无法自拔
... he wouldn't mind getting a cup of coffee.
他大概想和你喝杯咖啡什么的
Ross? All this time? I've gotta talk to him.
罗斯?这些日子以来?我得找他谈谈
-He's in China! -The country.
-可他现在中国! -那个国家
Is his flight gone?
她的飞机起飞了吗?
Yes! He's watching a woman do this:
是的!他正在看一个女人做这个:
He's gone!
他走了!
His flight doesn't leave for 45 minutes.
他的飞机再过45分钟才会起飞
-What about time difference? -From here to the airport?
-时差呢? -从这儿到机场?
-You'll never make it! -I've gotta try.
-你赶不上的! -我得试试
What'll you say to him?
瑞秋,你要对他说什么?
-I don't know. -Then you shouldn't go.
-我也不知道 -那么或许你不该去
Right. If you're gonna break his heart,that can wait.
没错,因为你是去伤他的心,不妨再等等
But if it's good,tell him now.
对,但如果是好消息,你得立刻去
-Maybe I'll know when I see him. -All right,does this help?
-或许见到面时我就知道 -这个有帮助吗?
No. Look,all I know is,I cannot wait a week. This is just too big.
没有,我只知道我等不了一星期, 这件事太严重了
I've just gotta talk to him. Okay,I'll see you later.
我得和他谈谈,再见了
Rachel,I love you! Deal with me first!
瑞秋,我爱你.先跟我把事情解决
All right.
好吧
-Ross! Excuse me,pardon me. -Your boarding pass?
-罗斯,抱歉 -请出示登机证
I need to talk to my friend.
我没有,我只是想找我朋友
Sorry,you're not allowed here without a pass.
抱歉,除非有登机证,否则不能进人
He's right there, in the blue jacket! Can l?
他就在那儿,穿蓝色夹克
I'm sorry. Federal regulations!
对不起,不行,联邦法规
Then could you please just give him a message for me?
好吧,能请你传话给他?
-This is very important. -All right. What's the message?
-这件事非常重要 -好吧,请说
I don't know.
我也不知道
Excuse me,sir! Excuse me,sir? I have a message for you.
抱歉,先生!有人叫我传话给你
Rachel loved the present. She'll see you when you get back.
是瑞秋!她说她喜欢你送的礼物 你回来后她想见你
What?
什么?
Toby,I don't know what she's talking about.
桃伊,拜托,我不懂她在说什么
There's no Rachel. Don't give me that deep freeze.
我不认识瑞秋,别给我脸色看
Oh,Joey,Joey,Joey!
哦,乔伊,乔伊,乔伊!
I think I blacked out there for a minute.
我想我爽昏了啊
It was nothing.
这不算什么
Well,now we gotta find something fun for you.
现在让我来伺候你
You know what?
你知道吗?
Forget about me. Let's give you another turn.
别管我了,我再伺候你一回
-Me,again? -Sure. Why not?
-又是我? -当然,有何不可?
Boy,somebody's gonna get a big fruit basket tomorrow!
明天有人会收到大水果篮!
I gotta tell you,you are nothing like I thought you'd be.
我得告诉你,你不像我想像中的那样
How do you mean?
什么意思?
I had you pegged as a guy who's always,"Me,me,me!"
大概是我认为,你是只顾自己享受的人
But you,you're a giver.
但你是个乐于付出的人
You're the most generous man I ever met.
你是我见过最慷慨的人
I mean,you're practically a woman.
你简直就是个女人
-You're just saying that. -No.
-你刚刚说了那个 -不
A woman!
一个女人
-So? -I missed him.
-所以? -我错过了
-I'm so sorry. -That's too bad.
-我很抱歉 -这太糟了
Yeah,right.
是的
No,I feel bad for her. I do.
不,我觉得对她不好,我真的这么认为
I can think of somebody other than myself.
我可以考虑其他人多过考虑我自己
All right,I'm going to bed.
好吧,我要去睡觉了
-Happy birthday. Hang in there. -Thanks.
-生日快乐.保持状态 -谢谢
Yes!
好啊!
Pizza coupons.
匹萨优惠券
Okay. You guys want help cleaning up this mess?
你们小伙打算帮忙清理这里吗?
That'd be great.
不错
So,Rach,you wanna save this wrapping paper?
瑞秋,这包装纸要留下来吗?
Are you gonna go for it with Ross or should I throw it out?
你要为罗斯留下,还是要我丢掉?
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道,我不知道
Thought about it all the way there...
我左思右想
...and I thought about it all the way back. You know,it's Ross!
我左思右想,你知道的,罗斯
You know what I mean? It's Ross.
你知道什么我什么意思?就是罗斯了
-Sure! -Sure.
-当然! -当然
I don't know. This is just my initial gut feeling...
我不知道,这是我内心深处的感受
... but I'm thinking it'd be really great.
我想这样应该会很不错
Oh,my God,me too! We'd be like friends-in-law!
天啊,我也是这样想 这样我们就成了亲戚兼朋友
The best part is you already know all about him.
你知道最棒的是什么?最棒的就是你已对他了如指掌
You start on the 1 5th date.
就好像从第15次约会开始
But it would be like starting on the 1 5th date.
对,但这就像从第15次约会开始
Another good point.
这观点也不错
I mean,on the 1 5th date, you're already in a very...
不,在第15次约会时,感情已
... "relationship-y" place. You're committed.
相当深厚,你们已经定下来了
What happens if it doesn't work out?
如果感情破裂该怎么办?
-Why isn't it working out? -Sometimes it doesn't.
-为何会感情破裂? -感情是勉强不来的
Is he not cute enough? Does he not make enough money?
你不觉得他帅?他钱赚得不够多?
-No,I'm just -Maybe there's someone else.
-不,我只是 -或许是另有其人?
-ls there someone else? -No,there is no one else.
-另有其人? -没有,没有另有其人
Then why are you dumping my brother?
那么你为何甩掉我哥?
Hey,big Spender!
大…挥霍者
She's still asleep.
她还在睡觉
-So how'd it go? -You know how you think you're great?
-情况如何? -你有没有老觉得自己床上功夫不错?
The fact you'd even ask shows how little you know me.
你会问这种问题,表示你根本不了解我
Last night I couldn't do the thing that usually makes me great.
昨晚我不能做让自己满足的事
So I had to do all this other stuff.
因此我得搬出全套功夫
And the response I got! Man,oh,man!
结果我得到什么回应?
It was like a ticker-tape parade!
就像是盛大的游行
I know. My room's very,very close to the parade route.
我明白,游行发生时,我的房间就非常接近游行路线
It was amazing,and not just for her. For me too!
这简直是太神奇了,而且不只是对她,对我也一样
It's like,all of a sudden I'm blind...
我就好像突然失明
... but all my other senses are heightened.
但其他的感官却更加的敏感
It's like I was able to appreciate it...
好像我达到…
...on another level.
…更高的境界
-I didn't know you had another level. -I know. Neither did l!
-我不知道你还有更高的境界. -我懂,我自己也不知道
Is something going on with O.J.?
O.J有活动?
Hey,great skirt. Birthday present?
漂亮的裙子,生日礼物?
-From who? -You.
-谁送的? -你
I exchanged the blouse you got me.
我将你送的衬衫改成的
Well,it's the thought.
真聪明
Doesn't Ross'flight get in in a couple hours? At gate 27B?
罗斯的飞机不是再过几小时就要抵达?27-b门?
Yeah. Monica,you know,I've been thinking about it.
对,摩尼卡,我一直在想
I've decided this Ross thing is not a good idea.
我虽决定和罗斯在一起,但这样或许不好
Why?
为什么?
I feel like I wouldn't just be going out with him.
因为我感觉,我不只是和他出去
I'd be going out with all of you. There'd be pressure
而是和你们大家一起出去,因为压力…
No pressure,no pressure!
不,没有压力.没有压力…
Nothing has happened, and you're already so
八字都还没一撇你就…
I'm not "so." Okay,I was a teensy bit weird at first...
我没有,开始我也觉得有点奇怪
... but I'll be good. I promise.
但我没事的,我保证
-Who is it? -It's me,Carl.
-是谁? -是我,卡尔
-Come on up. -Behind my brother's back?
-上来! -背着我哥?
Is the kind of crazy thing you won't be hearing from me.
我就不做出这种疯狂事
-Seven hundred bucks! -All right,you did it!
-七百块! -你办到了!
Do we have any fruit?
我们有水果可吃吗?
Man,hell of a two weeks.
折腾了两星期
You know what? I feel I learned something.
我感觉自己学到了一些
You'll stick with this "all for her" thing?
这么说你将继续“牺牲小我完成大我”?
What are you,crazy?
你疯了不成
When a blind man gets his sight back, does he walk around like this?
瞎人重新见光明后会这样走路吗?
If I see one more picture of Ed Begley Jr...
我是说如果我再看见艾德贝格拉二世
...in that stupid electric car, I'm gonna shoot myself!
在那电车上,我就举枪自尽
I'm not against environmental issues,per se...
别误会我的意思,我个人并不反对环保
...it's just that guy!
只是我讨厌那家伙
I can't believe you'd rather go out with him than me.
我难以相信你跟他约会,而不是跟我
Excuse me,I'm trying to have a date here.
抱歉,我正在约会
Fine. Just stop thinking about me.
行,那就别再想我
Can't do it,can you?
办不到,对不?
I'm thinking about you. So what?
我想你,那又怎样?
I don't get it. What do you see in this guy?
我不懂你为何会选上这种人?
Happens to be a very nice guy.
他像是个好男人
I mean,come on,buddy! Get a real car!
老兄,买台真正的车吧
Rachel,come on. Give us a chance.
瑞秋,给我一个机会吧
Ross,it's too hard.
罗斯,太难了
Why,because it'll get weird for everyone else? This is about us.
为什么?因为大家会感觉不对劲?这是我们两人的事
I've been in love with you since the ninth grade.
我从九年级开始就爱上你
You're like my best friend. If we broke up,and I lost you
罗斯,你像是我最要好的朋友 我知道如果分手我将失去你
What makes you think that?
不,你为何认为我们会分手?
Have you been involved where you haven't broken up?
曾和你在一起人不是都和你分手了
No.
不
But it only has to happen once.
但这种事只会发生一次
You and I both know we are perfect for each other. Right?
你我都知道我们是天生的一对
So the only question is: Are you attracted to me?
唯一的问题是:你对我有感觉吗?
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean,I've never looked at you that way before.
我从未以那种方式看你
Well,start looking.
那就开始看吧
-Wow. -Exactly!
-喔. -准确!
And I'm gonna be the guy...
没错,我就是那个
...caught behind this hammerhead in traffic!
被困在车阵中的家伙
Right! You're right.
对…你是对的
You know what?
你知道吗?
I'm supposed to pick up a friend at the airport.
我本应该去机场接朋友
I am so sorry!
真是抱歉
If you wanna finish your drinks, please do.
如果你想在这儿继续喝,请便
-I'm sorry,I gotta go. I'm sorry. -But....
-但我得走了,抱歉 -可是
-Where are you going? -To get Ross.
-你要去哪? -去接罗斯
-My God,this is so exciting! -I know.
-天哪,这太令人兴奋了! -我知道
If you want the rest of my date, I'm not gonna finish it.
如果你希望和我继续剩下的约会,我要结束这个
-Rachel,he's not a sandwich. -No,he's a banker with opera tickets.
-瑞秋,他不是三明治. -不,他是一个有剧院的银行家
Hello!
你好!
-Where you going? -Airport.
-你要去哪? -机场
You can't tell him. There's so much I haven't done.
你不能告诉他,有太多的事情我没有去做
I haven't watched Baywatch with Yasmine Bleeth!
我还没有看“海湾女郎”呢!
Chandler,relax. This is a good going to the airport.
钱德,轻松点,这是一个好的接机
Oh,well then fly,good woman, fly like the wind.
哦,好吧,飞吧,好女人,像风一样飞吧
-I'm flying! -Tell him I'm the one who blew it!
-我在飞也! -告诉他是我吹的风!
Yes,another successful case for the love doctor.
好吧,另外一个爱情博士的成功案例
Excuse me! Pardon me. Excuse me. Sorry.
对不起!对不起
Toby,for God's sake, will you let it go?
桃伊,别再胡思乱想了
There's no Rachel!
没有瑞秋这个人
Hey! I got that.
嘿,我拿到了
-Thanks,sweetie. -No problem.
-谢谢 -不客气
I can't wait for you to meet my friends.
我迫不及待、想将你介绍给我朋友
You don't think they'll judge me?
你不认为他们会评断我、取笑我?
-No,they will. I just.... -Can't wait!
-他们会的,我只是… -但我实在是等不及
Come on,they're gonna love you.
他们一定会喜欢你的
-==六人行第一季完==- -=敬请期待第二季=- -bbs.btbbt.com-